
Clues = new Mongo.Collection("clues");

Clues.insert({
	category: "GAMES",
	clues: [{
		question: "mario's brother",
		answer: "luigi",
	},
	{
		question: "halo guy",
		answer: "master chief",
	},
	{
		question: "purple luigi",
		answer: "waluigi",
	},
	{
		question: "yellow mario",
		answer: "wario",
	},
	{
		question: "master chief gf",
		answer: "cortana",
	}]
	
});

Clues.insert({
	category: "GAMES",
	clues: [{
		question: "mario's brother",
		answer: "luigi",
	},
	{
		question: "halo guy",
		answer: "master chief",
	},
	{
		question: "purple luigi",
		answer: "waluigi",
	},
	{
		question: "yellow mario",
		answer: "wario",
	},
	{
		question: "master chief gf",
		answer: "cortana",
	}]
	
});

Clues.insert({
	category: "GAMES",
	clues: [{
		question: "mario's brother",
		answer: "luigi",
	},
	{
		question: "halo guy",
		answer: "master chief",
	},
	{
		question: "purple luigi",
		answer: "waluigi",
	},
	{
		question: "yellow mario",
		answer: "wario",
	},
	{
		question: "master chief gf",
		answer: "cortana",
	}]
	
});

Clues.insert({
	category: "GAMES",
	clues: [{
		question: "mario's brother",
		answer: "luigi",
	},
	{
		question: "halo guy",
		answer: "master chief",
	},
	{
		question: "purple luigi",
		answer: "waluigi",
	},
	{
		question: "yellow mario",
		answer: "wario",
	},
	{
		question: "master chief gf",
		answer: "cortana",
	}]
	
});

Clues.insert({
	category: "GAMES",
	clues: [{
		question: "mario's brother",
		answer: "luigi",
	},
	{
		question: "halo guy",
		answer: "master chief",
	},
	{
		question: "purple luigi",
		answer: "waluigi",
	},
	{
		question: "yellow mario",
		answer: "wario",
	},
	{
		question: "master chief gf",
		answer: "cortana",
	}]
	
});

Clues.insert({
	category: "GAMES",
	clues: [{
		question: "mario's brother",
		answer: "luigi",
	},
	{
		question: "halo guy",
		answer: "master chief",
	},
	{
		question: "purple luigi",
		answer: "waluigi",
	},
	{
		question: "yellow mario",
		answer: "wario",
	},
	{
		question: "master chief gf",
		answer: "cortana",
	}]
	
});
	
